[
    {
        "question": "The dense network of railways is found in …………..",
        "options": [
            "Indian plateau",
            "The coastal plain",
            "North Indian plain"
        ],
        "answer":3 
    },
    {
        "question": "There are plenty of opportunities for tourism in India considering the …………. of the country",
        "options": [
            "Temples",
            "Natural beauty",
            "Heritage"
        ],
        "answer":3 
    },
    {
        "question": "Which part of India has less means of Transport",
        "options": [
            "Northern Mountain Region",
            "Indian Plateau Region",
            "The Coastal Region"
        ],
        "answer":1 
    },
    {
        "question": "Name the city through which IST passes.",
        "options": [
            "Lucknow",
            "Banaras",
            "Allahabad"
        ],
        "answer":3 
    },
    {
        "question": "In Brazil ………….. waterways are not well developed.",
        "options": [
            "Inland",
            "Sea",
            "Ocean"
        ],
        "answer":1 
    },
    {
        "question": "Identify the odd one.",
        "options": [
            "Satellite",
            "Internet",
            "Mobile",
            "Planets"
        ],
        "answer":4 
    },
    {
        "question": "Waterways are the ………….. mode of transport.",
        "options": [
            "Cheapest",
            "Quickest",
            "Fastest"
        ],
        "answer":1 
    },
    {
        "question": "IST is …………. of GMT",
        "options": [
            "Behind",
            "Ahead",
            "Same"
        ],
        "answer":2 
    },
    {
        "question": "How many hours the BRT is behind GMT",
        "options": [
            "5",
            "2",
            "3"
        ],
        "answer":3 
    },
    {
        "question": "Brazil has the ………….. bio-diversity in the world.",
        "options": [
            "Least",
            "Largest",
            "Smallest"
        ],
        "answer":2 
    },
    {
        "question": "The south east part of Brazil has dense network of railways because.",
        "options": [
            "It’s densely populated area",
            "It has a cool climate",
            "It is a plain area"
        ],
        "answer":3 
    },
    {
        "question": "Brazil follows ………….. time zones in the country",
        "options": [
            "1",
            "4",
            "4",
            ""
        ],
        "answer":2 
    },
    {
        "question": "The prominent highway of Brazil is …………… highway",
        "options": [
            "Trans - Atlantic",
            "Trans - Amazonian",
            "Trans - Australian"
        ],
        "answer":2 
    },
    {
        "question": "Freight and passenger Transport has been facilitators due to the development of ………….",
        "options": [
            "Roadways",
            "Railways",
            "Airways"
        ],
        "answer":2 
    }                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                    
]